http://www.campus-classics.com/pages/privacy-policy

Small parcel delivery delays are expected throughout December, especially as we get closer to the holidays. Shop early to ensure your items arrive in time. Sign up for Informed Delivery® by USPS® to receive real-time updates and manage your deliveries.
Sorority Accessories
Hats
Bags
Sorority Gifts
Gift Ideas
Items Under $20
Office & Study
Auto Accessories
Big Little Tees
Custom Orders
Adventure Apparel
Search
Fraternity
Alpha Epsilon Pi (AEPi)
Alpha Gamma Rho (AGR)
Alpha Sigma Phi (Alpha Sig)
Alpha Tau Omega (ATO)
Beta Theta Pi (Beta)
Chi Phi
Delta Chi
Delta Sigma Phi (Delta Sig)
Delta Tau Delta (Delt)
Delta Upsilon (DU)
Kappa Alpha Order
Kappa Delta Rho (KDR)
Kappa Sigma
Lambda Chi Alpha
Phi Delta Theta
Phi Gamma Delta (FIJI)
Phi Kappa Psi (Phi Psi)
Phi Kappa Tau (Phi Tau)
Pi Kappa Alpha (Pike)
Sigma Alpha Epsilon (SAE)
Sigma Chi
Sigma Nu
Sigma Phi Epsilon (SigEp)
Sigma Pi
Sigma Tau Gamma
Tau Kappa Epsilon (TKE)
Theta Chi
Zeta Beta Tau (ZBT)
Sorority
Alpha Chi Omega (Alpha Chi)
Alpha Delta Pi (ADPi)
Alpha Gamma Delta (Alpha Gam)
Alpha Omicron Pi (AOII)
Alpha Phi
Alpha Xi Delta (AXiD)
Chi Omega (Chi O)
Delta Delta Delta (Tri Delta)
Delta Gamma
Delta Zeta
Gamma Phi Beta
Kappa Alpha Theta (Theta)
Kappa Delta
Kappa Kappa Gamma (Kappa)
Pi Beta Phi (Pi Phi)
Sigma Kappa
Sigma Sigma Sigma (Tri Sigma)
Zeta Tau Alpha (ZTA)
All Products
All Fraternity
All Sorority
Fraternity Top Picks
New!
Holiday Picks
Stocking Stuffers
Holiday Tees
Personalized Items
Comfort Colors
Retriever Tees
Adventure Apparel Lifestyle Tees
Retro
Sorority Top Picks
New!
Holiday Picks
Stocking Stuffers
Comfort Colors
Holiday Tees
Retriever Tees
Retro
Patriotic Collection
Sale & Clearance
Fraternity
Alpha Epsilon Pi (AEPi)
Alpha Gamma Rho (AGR)
Alpha Sigma Phi (Alpha Sig)
Alpha Tau Omega (ATO)
Beta Theta Pi (Beta)
Chi Phi
Delta Chi
Delta Sigma Phi (Delta Sig)
Delta Tau Delta (Delt)
Delta Upsilon (DU)
Kappa Alpha Order
Kappa Delta Rho (KDR)
Kappa Sigma
Lambda Chi Alpha
Phi Delta Theta
Phi Gamma Delta (FIJI)
Phi Kappa Psi (Phi Psi)
Phi Kappa Tau (Phi Tau)
Pi Kappa Alpha (Pike)
Sigma Alpha Epsilon (SAE)
Sigma Chi
Sigma Nu
Sigma Phi Epsilon (SigEp)
Sigma Pi
Sigma Tau Gamma
Tau Kappa Epsilon (TKE)
Theta Chi
Zeta Beta Tau (ZBT)
Sorority
Alpha Chi Omega (Alpha Chi)
Alpha Delta Pi (ADPi)
Alpha Gamma Delta (Alpha Gam)
Alpha Omicron Pi (AOII)
Alpha Phi
Alpha Xi Delta (AXiD)
Chi Omega (Chi O)
Delta Delta Delta (Tri Delta)
Delta Gamma
Delta Zeta
Gamma Phi Beta
Kappa Alpha Theta (Theta)
Kappa Delta
Kappa Kappa Gamma (Kappa)
Pi Beta Phi (Pi Phi)
Sigma Kappa
Sigma Sigma Sigma (Tri Sigma)
Zeta Tau Alpha (ZTA)
All Products
All Fraternity
All Sorority
Fraternity Top Picks
New!
Holiday Picks
Stocking Stuffers
Holiday Tees
Personalized Items
Comfort Colors
Retriever Tees
Adventure Apparel Lifestyle Tees
Retro
Sorority Top Picks
New!
Holiday Picks
Stocking Stuffers
Comfort Colors
Holiday Tees
Retriever Tees
Retro
Patriotic Collection
Sale & Clearance
Log in OR Create account
Modern information gathering is crucial to the operation of our internet order fulfillment activities, and your privacy is honored and valued. You can access and browse our website without disclosing any personal information. We do not enable any communication with other site visitors or the ability to post information that can be accessed by others.
How Do We Collect Personal Information?
We collect information directly from the relevant individual through their created account or using following technologies:
"Cookies" are data files that are placed on your device or computer and often include an anonymous unique identifier. For more information about cookies, and how to disable cookies, visit http://www.allaboutcookies.org. “Log files” track actions occurring on the site, and collect data including your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, and date/time stamps. “Web beacons,” “tags,” and “pixels” are electronic files used to record information about how you browse the site.
How Do We Use the Information Collected?
We use the information that you provide to fulfill your online order, provide correspondence regarding any orders placed, and provide shipping and tracking information. Additionally, we use this information to optimize or improve our website, provide you with information or advertising relating to our products through our email subscription list. Any promotional materials sent by mail or email are only from Campus Classics and are related to items that you have purchased in the past. To remove yourself from our mailing or email list, contact us at questions@campus-classics.com, or click unsubscribe in any promotional email.
We do not research data about our visitors from other sources such as public records, social media, or private organizations. Information put into our website is protected from unauthorized access by Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption. Our internal security policies and technical measures protect the personal data we have from unauthorized access, improper use or disclosure, unauthorized modification, and unlawful destruction or accidental loss. All employees and data processors that have access to the use of personal data are obligated to respect the confidentiality of our visitors' personal data. We ensure that your personal data will not be disclosed to State institutions or authorities except, and only, if required by law or other regulation. To access, update, delete, or obtain a copy of the information we have for you, email questions@campus-classics.com.
© 2020, Campus Classics
Secure Shopping
We know how important security is, so you can place your order with confidence.
All of the information you share with us online is encrypted by what is called a Secured Socket Layer, or SSL.
You can see this for yourself!
You know that a web site has SSL when the URL begins with https:// rather than just http://.
Also you will find an icon of a locked padlock.
It is usually found near the URL bar, but may be in a different location depending upon your browser.
With state of the art 256-bit SSL technology, your important data is encrypted before it even leaves your computer.
Your credit card transaction is handled directly with our processing service; no employee of Campus Classics ever has access to credit card numbers entered online.
We’re also easy to find!
We have been headquartered in Indianapolis, Indiana since our founding in 1989.
You can call and speak with one of our friendly staff members and we’ll be happy to help in any way we can.
Satisfaction Guarantee
We want you to love what you ordered from us. That's why we kept your best interests in mind as a customer when we created our policies.
Hassle Free Returns and Exchanges
You can order with confidence knowing that you can return and exchange most items that you've ordered! Please read our returns and exchanges policy for more information.
Address Corrections
If you need to update the shipping address in your order and it hasn’t shipped, we can still make changes for you! Please call us at 800-274-7335 or email us at questions@campus-classics.com with your order information and we'll work with you to get this updated.
Order Cancellations
If your order hasn’t shipped and you'd like to cancel it for any reason, we're able to cancel this for you. Please call us at 800-274-7335 or email us at questions@campus-classics.com with your order information to request an order cancellation. If your order has already been shipped, please see our returns and exchanges page for information on returning your order!
Damaged or Incorrect Items
If your item(s) come damaged or incorrect, we want to make it right. Please email us with your name, order number, and a picture to verify, and we'll issue you a return label. We want you to love what you ordered!
Have any questions? Please see our contact us or FAQ pages for more information.
You are being redirected...
We are very pleased to announce the new Kappa Sigma Official Store, powered by Campus Classics®!
By clicking the continue button below, you will now be redirected to the Kappa Sigma Official Store located at https://www.kappasigmastore.com
The Kappa Sigma Official Store will open in a new tab, allowing you to return to the Campus Classics website in this tab to shop for any of the other Fraternity or Sorority groups we currently offer products for.
CANCEL
CONTINUE
Net Orders Checkout
Item
Price
Qty
Total
Subtotal
Mozambique
Myanmar (Burma)
Namibia
Nauru
Nepal
Netherlands
Netherlands Antilles
New Caledonia
New Zealand
Nicaragua
Zimbabwe
AlabamaAlaskaAmerican SamoaArizonaArkansasCaliforniaColoradoConnecticutDelawareDistrict of ColumbiaFederated States of MicronesiaFloridaGeorgiaGuamHawaiiIdahoIllinoisIndianaIowaKansasKentuckyLouisianaMaineMarshall IslandsMarylandMassachusettsMichiganMinnesotaMississippiMissouriMontanaNebraskaNevadaNew HampshireNew JerseyNew MexicoNew YorkNorth CarolinaNorth DakotaNorthern Mariana IslandsOhioOklahomaOregonPalauPennsylvaniaPuerto RicoRhode IslandSouth CarolinaSouth DakotaTennesseeTexasUtahVermontVirgin IslandsVirginiaWashingtonWest VirginiaWisconsinWyomingArmed Forces AmericasArmed Forces EuropeArmed Forces Pacific
Shipping Methods
